[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
[In my prime]
[Episode 14]
Make way, make way.
Slow down. Be careful.
It'll be fine.
Be careful, please.
Doctor,
you have to save my son.
He's still so young.
He can't die.
Doctor.
Doctor, my brother is an athlete.
You must save his leg,
doctor!
Please calm down.
We'll do our best.
You may
wait outside,
okay? Trust us.
Mom, Mom.
Help your mom sit down.
Mom.
Come on, sit down.
Honey, stay strong.
Our son is a lucky guy.
He'll be fine.
Mom.
Why are you here?
You didn't go to take the exam?
Feed her some water.
I was really afraid her brother
would be beaten to death!
But I didn't expect that
Qi Shi would skip the exam.
What were you thinking?
Why didn't you call the police when you
saw Qi Zhi getting beaten?
What was the point of telling Qi Shi?
What could she do over there?
I was also panicking at the time.
If I were half as composed as you,
would I come in last
on every exam?
W-Where are you going?
To find Qi Shi.
The last science exam is worth 300 points.
You completely ruined
Qi Shi's bright future!
Qi Shi!
Calm down!
You can't catch up.
Your leg is doing well enough
for you to get out of bed now.
Let it heal properly,
and it should be fine.
But
the hairline fracture
has a risk of reinjury.
After a comprehensive evaluation,
we advise you to quit running.
Qi Zhi,
you can't represent
the provincial team to compete anymore.
But it's okay.
You can still be
a PE teacher in the future.
Zhou Xuanyu!
Zhou Xuanyu, get the hell out here!
Don't hide in your house
like a coward!
Zhou Xuanyu!
I know you're home!
Get the hell out here, you bastard!
I'm right here.
Boss,
why do you keep hiding from that idiot?
What makes you think
I'm hiding from him?
We were detained for days.
You want to go back in?
We need to be
law-abiding citizens.
Understand?
Understood.
Boss, you
just don't want to waste your time
on that idiot.
Zhou Xuanyu!
Oh, no! There's a fire!
Boss.
Boss,
looks like smoke is coming
from your house.
Qi Zhi, you bastard!
Call the police now!
There's a fire!
Qi Zhi!
The Zhous' house is on fire!
You must have got the wrong person.
With his seriously injured leg,
he couldn't be the one who set the fire.
You must have got the wrong person.
Yes, officer.
There's no way
my son did this.
We'll figure out
whether he did it or not
when we get to the station.
Take him away.
Wait, Zhi.
Zhi, say something. Zhi...
Did you do it, Zhi?
Tell the police.
Zhi, speak up!
Say something!
Qi Zhi, say something.
Qi Zhi, you acted too impulsively!
You ruined your own future
as well as our family.
Do you know that, Qi Zhi?
Officers,
I'm begging you on my knees.
Don't take him away.
Mom!
Mom, don't do this.
Don't interfere with our duties.
Mom...
Get up, come on.
Do not interfere with our work,
please.
I'll go take a look.
Si, I'm going with you.
I'll
also go ask around
and see what exactly happened.
Grab a bite before you go.
I'm not eating.
Qi Zhi
was destined to face this ordeal.
Zhao,
we need
to expedite this case.
Mom.
Officer,
how is my son doing?
Can I see him?
Suspects aren't allowed
to see their families
in criminal detention.
Even prisoners are allowed family visits.
Why can't we see him?
Exactly.
Please let us see him just once.
We're his family.
We need to know what's going on.
Yes, officer,
please just let us see him.
I know him well.
He wouldn't do such a thing.
You must investigate this thoroughly.
Officer,
will my brother really be sentenced?
The case is currently
under investigation.
We'll contact you
once we have confirmed information.
Please go home and wait for our update.
Well...
Mrs. Huo.
Don't worry.
The police will definitely figure it out.
Qi Zhi will be fine for sure.
Don't worry.
-Dong Fang.
-Dad.
Did you get any news?
Isn't Liu's child
a lawyer?
I told her the details
about Qi Zhi's case.
She said
it's considered arson.
What... What now?
It's all my fault.
Were it not for me,
Qi Zhi wouldn't...
Don't overthink it.
I've already told Qi Shi
to find a lawyer
and see if there's any way
to help Qi Zhi.
Lawyer Liu,
you must help my brother.
Here.
Under Article 114
of the Criminal Law,
where an act of arson
has not caused serious consequences,
the sentencing range
is 3
to 10 years in prison.
This is exactly
Qi Zhi's current situation.
There is a way.
I can draft a letter
of forgiveness.
If we can get the victim
to sign this letter,
showing they
forgive what
the suspect did,
then in judicial practice,
the court can
consider it
as a discretionary circumstance
for a lighter sentence.
Y-You mean,
he could get a lighter sentence?
Zhou the Stingy Fat Cat hates our guts.
How could he forgive him?
Here's the thing.
The lawyer suggested Zhi
write an apology letter.
This way, there's a better chance
of getting the Zhou family's forgiveness.
However...
However, with Qi Zhi's temper,
getting him to write
an apology letter to the Zhous
is next to impossible.
Lawyer Liu.
How did it go, Lawyer Liu?
Did Qi Zhi write the apology letter?
I've handled plenty of cases,
but this is the first time
I've met someone as stubborn as Qi Zhi.
He said
he'd rather spend
a few more years in prison
than apologize to Zhou.
Is he crazy?
How can he still be
so stubborn at this point?
An apology letter is crucial to getting
the victim's letter of forgiveness.
But Qi Zhi just wouldn't cooperate.
I'm afraid you, as his family members,
have to figure out a way
to talk
the victim into it.
Hey, Qi!
Why are you two still here?
I told you,
Mr. Zhou
is currently in a meeting
and has no time to see you.
How about you two go back first,
and I'll call you
when he's free?
We're not leaving.
If he doesn't come today,
he'll have to come tomorrow.
We'll just wait here
every day anyway.
He has to come to work sooner or later.
We'll just wait here.
Why are you so stubborn?
Mr. Zhou, are you heading out?
Mr. Zhou!
Mr. Zhou! Mr. Zhou!
Mr. Zhou...
Put some of this on.
Your dad said...
Your dad said winters in Beining
are freezing cold.
You have to wear the kind of...
down jackets
that cover you from head to ankles,
right?
He said he'd buy one for Zhi.
Buy that down jacket...
Look, the down jacket is here.
Where is Zhi?
Where is my son?
Qi Shi...
I'm not having a nightmare, am I?
Mom.
He was about to make it
into the provincial team.
How did our son...
and our family...
end up like this?
I told you long ago
to keep them apart.
But...
But Qi Zhi just wouldn't listen.
And you all
also went against me,
didn't you?
Cao Si... She's really something.
This girl's impressive... Well...
She really ruined...
ruined our whole family.
Mom, well...
Cao Si is not the one to blame.
Who else could it be other than her?
Would your brother
have been screwed otherwise?
Would you not even
have made it into the exam room?
I told the two of them
to break up...
Cao Si was just capable
of keeping your brother hooked.
Yes, your brother acted on impulse.
He fought and set a fire.
He...
But who did he do it for?
For who?
Mom, what are you doing?
Mom!
Mom, come back!
Cao Si!
You jinx! You...
My son ended up in this state
all because of you!
You're always flirting with one guy
and another!
If you want to be a fortune-hunter,
then go ahead!
Why did you have to ruin my son?
Why did you have to ruin Qi Zhi?
Her words are too harsh, Grandpa.
I'm going to talk to Mrs. Huo.
Just let her curse.
Dad, come on, go stop her.
The neighbors are watching.
Would my son have gone
to fight someone?
Just let her curse.
Would he have set a fire
and burned someone's house down?
I still haven't even
been able to see him!
Si,
don't be sad.
Listen to me.
Just let it go in one ear
and out the other.
Don't you know
Mrs. Huo Qinglian's temper?
Yeah, Si,
don't be sad.
Dad is already trying
to find a way, isn't he?
I heard that as long as the Zhou family
signs the letter of forgiveness,
Qi Zhi might still have a chance.
A world champion...
He was going to be a world champion!
His leg is injured,
and the provincial team
doesn't want him anymore.
Cao Si...
Cao Si!
You've ruined
our family!
No, Dad, go stop her!
Her words are too harsh!
People might be laughing at us.
Hurry up! Come on!
Go now!
Go stop her!
Enough.
You've scolded enough.
Let's go home.
Don't make a scene
in front of the neighbors.
I just want the neighbors to see
what the Cao family
did to us
and how they bully our family,
young and old.
Mom, come on.
Will your cursing
bring Zhi back?
Your brother is only 22!
22!
His life is ruined.
Ruined...
Aren't we
trying to figure out a way?
Just scrape the money together
and beg for forgiveness.
What else can we do?
Life goes on!
All right, stop looking.
There's nothing to see.
Stop staring!
There's nothing to see!
Mr. Zhou.
Cao Dongfang?
What?
Are you here to plead for Qi Zhi, too?
Yeah.
Mr. Zhou, Mr. Zhou,
I watched this kid grow up.
He's been a sensible, good kid
since childhood.
But this time...
I don't know what happened this time.
Just a while ago,
he won the championship
at the Provincial Games
and was selected by the provincial team.
If it weren't for this case,
he'd definitely be training
with the provincial team now
and might even
win glory for our country in the future.
Mr. Zhou, look,
considering we are
colleagues, could you please
cut him some slack
and give him another chance?
Cut him some slack?
Do you think
the law can cut him some slack?
He set fire
to my house.
That's a criminal offense!
If the fire hadn't been put out quickly,
it could have spread
to the neighbors
and caused a disaster.
I know.
It's a blatant disregard
for the law!
Whether he's a provincial champion
or an Olympic champion,
I'm sending him to jail!
Yes, yes. But he's young, isn't he?
It's normal for young people
to make mistakes, right?
Besides, we are all his...
Go away! Get out of here!
Mr. Zhou.
Okay.
It's so hot today.
Why did you close the door?
How's it?
Did the Zhou family agree to settle?
Si,
don't overthink it.
This has
absolutely nothing to do with you.
If it had nothing to do with me,
why would Mrs. Huo get so worked up?
Why does Dad keep going
to meet the Zhou family?
If it weren't for me,
Qi Zhi wouldn't have gotten kicked off
the provincial team
or ended up in jail.
Qi Shi.
How is your brother?
Si,
you'd better not
come to our house for a while.
Still awake?
Qi Aihua,
how could you
still be in the mood to drink?
I... I just drank this little bit.
Our son is in such big trouble.
As a grown man,
what else can you do besides drinking?
You're such a coward.
Are you even a man?
Indeed.
I'm a loser.
I'm a good-for-nothing.
I'm not like a man.
Do you think I feel okay about this?
I'm suffering, too.
With our family in such a big crisis,
I'm a grown man,
but I can't help at all.
I can't make much money. I...
I...
I can do nothing at all.
Qi Zhi is in such big trouble,
and I can't even protect him if I want to.
I am incompetent and good for nothing!
I'm a loser... A loser...
It's all the Cao family's fault.
None of them are
any good.
Cao Dongfang used that little favor
he did for you back then
to take our son with him.
These years,
every time I saw our son
having a good time at his place,
it just...
just killed me inside.
It hurt so much.
But look at him.
We raised Qi Shi
with so much effort
and suffered so much.
Has he ever appreciated it?
You saw him
as a good buddy and treated him so well,
while he made a fool of you.
When your mine was restructured,
he reported you
without hesitation.
When he ruined your career,
did he care about your brotherhood
or our family's survival?
That's in the past. Let it slide.
Why bring it up again?
Let it slide? I can't.
I just can't let it go.
The most infuriating part
is about our son.
He was doing perfectly well,
worked so hard,
and finally got selected
for the provincial team.
But he threw everything away
just for Cao Si.
He gave up his future
and his family.
Everything...
Everything is ruined.
Fine.
Since the Cao family
won't let me live in peace,
I won't let them either.
I'm going to burn their house down, too.
Let me vent my anger.
Qinglian,
don't be crazy.
If you burn their house down,
how are we supposed to carry on?
Let's just all end our peaceful lives!
I'm going to tell everyone
what happened back then!
You...
Move aside!
What are you doing?
-Qinglian!
-Mom, your blood pressure medicine.
Qi Shi, you're back just in time.
Come with me.
Where to?
No, no...
Go back to your room.
Stay out of this.
Qi Aihua,
get out of my way!
What are you doing?
I'm going to tell them what happened
back then!
Mom! Mom!
Stop making a scene, okay?
Will you ever stop?
Honey, please don't leave.
I'm sorry.
I...
I was drunk.
Hit me.
Hit me however you want.
Hit me
as long as it makes you feel better.
Get away from me.
I'm sorry.
I promise
it won't happen again.
Look,
my hand is still shaking.
Honey.
Qi Zhi's in trouble,
but we still
have to move on.
We still have Qi Shi
and...
And Cao Xin.
♪ Bright moonlight ♪
Only if we stay strong
♪ Draws my gaze up to the night ♪
can Qi Zhi be okay.
♪ Though it falls right beside me ♪
No matter what the future holds,
♪ It feels empty ♪
as long as we don't give up,
♪ Just like you ♪
things will
get better one day.
♪ Your hands are warm to hold ♪
♪ But I often fail to see ♪
♪ The look in your eyes ♪
♪ Clearly I, in this dark ♪
♪ Endless dark ♪
♪ Have followed you all this way ♪
♪ Maybe I asked for too much ♪
♪ A path lit all the way ♪
♪ Only through love and choice ♪
♪ Do I see I've had it all ♪
Si,
did you come to me just for Qi Zhi?
How is he better than me?
He hit so hard.
♪ When you look at me, look at me ♪
I'm still in pain.
You struck first.
You're really wronging me this time.
I just wanted to have someone scare him.
Who knew he'd get serious immediately
♪ I don't really ask for much ♪
and whack us with his bag?
H-He got hurt
because he lost his balance.
Why did he take it out on me
and set fire to my house?
No matter what,
♪ You and the moonlight ♪
this
♪ Have already fulfilled my wish ♪
happened because of you.
♪ It's okay not to be perfect ♪
You've already ruined him once.
You can't ruin him a second time.
♪ When you look at me, look at me ♪
Si,
it's really not my call.
Our house was
just renovated two years ago.
My dad is still furious.
He said
the Qi family's case is non-negotiable.
They must pay the compensation,
and he must serve his time.
Everything will follow legal procedures.
Si, don't go.
My house
got burned down because of you.
I'll go beg my dad.
Just don't ignore me.
What's wrong with your back?
I just sprained it.
Is it here?
Relax, relax.
Let me rub it for you.
Be gentle.
Is it any better?
I'll buy you some pig trotters later
for recovery.
Dad,
since the Qi family has already
agreed to compensate us,
let's just
not push them too hard,
okay?
Besides, Qi Zhi will be in jail
for several years
to learn his lesson.
As businessmen,
we should be magnanimous.
Let's just sign this letter
of forgiveness
and do them a favor.
What do you think, Dad?
Did Cao Si ask you to talk to me?
Dad,
I already promised Si.
You must
sign this for me no matter what.
Otherwise, Si won't talk to me again.
I'm really into her.
It hurts, Dad!
It hurts!
You little brat!
Are you really
trying to piss me off?
Mr. Zhou.
Mr. Zhou!
Your family
really haunts me like ghosts.
I'm here today
to formally apologize to you
on behalf of my brother.
I hope you can
sign the letter of forgiveness.
This is about my brother's future.
An apology alone can settle this?
My house was burned
to the ground by your brother.
You want my forgiveness?
Even if your brother rots in jail,
it won't be enough for me.
Wait.
Whatever your losses are,
we'll compensate you.
It's really about my brother's future.
I'm begging you to give him a chance
to turn over a new leaf.
Give him a chance?
He broke the law.
Go ask the judge
if he'll give him a chance.
Mr. Zhou.
You know exactly why
he set that fire.
My brother's leg is seriously injured,
and his future is completely ruined.
You want to hold someone accountable?
Zhou Xuanyu provoked him first.
You can't say
it has nothing to do with him.
So?
Are you threatening me?
I'm here to negotiate a settlement.
As long as you sign this,
we can consider
letting Zhou Xuanyu off the hook.
You're really something, little girl.
Get in.
I need to talk to you.
We didn't have time to cook.
Let's just make do with this.
Where's Mom?
Your mom said she has no appetite.
She's lying in bed.
She hasn't had anything for two days.
How can her body take it?
Sweetie,
your mom and I have been
busy with Zhi's case these days.
We haven't had time to care about you.
You missed
such an important exam because of Zhi.
Are you very upset deep down inside?
I'm fine, Dad.
Just eat up.
I have no appetite either.
Take your time eating.
Are you...
alright?
Worst case, I'll just repeat the year.
What about Mr. Qi and Mrs. Huo?
How could they be alright?
You made these?
I spent all afternoon on them.
I saw Mrs. Huo making buns
pretty easily.
But when I tried it myself,
it was a totally different story.
It's my first time.
T-This is the best I could do.
I just feel that
Mr. Qi and Mrs. Huo
have been so good to me.
With our families in this situation now,
I want to do something for them.
Mom,
please grab a bite.
Cao Xin made these buns.
Cao Xin made them?
The filling is a bit salty.
And the dough was even unleavened.
Cao Xin has grown up.
He can even make buns now.
It's quite salty.
Mom, I'll go get you some water.
Your mom is just hungry.
Cao Xin has grown up.
But what about Qi Zhi?
His good life was ruined.
And Qi Shi,
you could have
gotten into a top university.
But because of Zhi's case,
you missed one exam.
What did our family do to deserve this?
The victim
gave me the letter of forgiveness.
With this letter,
the rest will be much easier.
Lawyer Liu,
you saved
our family.
The victim's cooperation is
thanks to your efforts
in persuading them, definitely.
I'm just doing my job.
I'll be meeting Qi Zhi in a bit.
Do you have any messages for him?
What is there to say?
Just tell him
to fully cooperate.
Since things have come to this point,
just don't think too much.
Ask him to eat well
and recover
from his injuries in there.
It's no big deal
if he can't be an athlete,
right?
We, as his parents, don't expect him
to be successful.
We j-just want to have him back home soon.
Thank you.
-Thank you.
-One more thing.
Tell him
not to get into any more fights in there.
That place has a motley crew.
Tell him to learn from his dad.
A real man knows
when to yield and when to stand tall.
Keep cool in trouble.
Walk away if he can't keep cool.
I'll pass all your words on to him.
Please tell my brother that
he still owes me a box of chocolates.
Got it.
Thank you.
You should have seen it.
She's like a completely different person
from head to toe.
I stared at her for a few minutes
and still couldn't believe it was her.